Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files K-O, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files L
    - Lewis, Edward H. Mrs. (Box A-73, Folder 287)
    - Lewis, Elma (Box A-73, Folder 288)
    - Lewis, Elsie M. Dr. (Box A-73, Folder 289)
      Photographer if identified: Post Office Department
    - Lewis, Emmanuel (Box A-73, Folder 290)
      Also one image removed from magazine.
    - Lewis, Edna (Box A-73, Folder 291)
    - Lewis, Eunice (Box A-73, Folder 292)
    - Lewis, Evelyn C. (Box A-73, Folder 293)
    - Lewis, Evelyn R. (Box A-73, Folder 294)
    - Lewis, Felton (Box A-73, Folder 295)
    - Lewis, Frances (Box A-73, Folder 296)
    - Lewis, Frank (Box A-73, Folder 297)
    - Lewis, Fred (Box A-73, Folder 298)
    - Lewis, Freddie (Box A-73, Folder 299)
    - Lewis, G. F. "Country" (Box A-73, Folder 300)
    - Lewis, Fulton E. Dr. (Box A-73, Folder 301)
    - Lewis, Furry (Box A-73, Folder 302)
    - Lewis, George (Ptl.) (Box A-73, Folder 303)
    - Lewis, George R. (Box A-73, Folder 304)
    - Lewis, Gilbert (Box A-73, Folder 305)
    - Lewis, Goldie (Box A-73, Folder 306)
    - Lewis, Greg (Box A-73, Folder 307)
    - Lewis, Grover (Box A-73, Folder 308)
    - Lewis, H. H. (Box A-73, Folder 309)
    - Lewis, Harry (Box A-73, Folder 310)
    - Lewis, Helynn Mrs. (Box A-73, Folder 311)
    - Lewis, Henry (Box A-73, Folder 312)
      Photographer if identified: The Picture Desk, Whitestone Photo, Amos Carr,
    - Lewis, Horace (Box A-74, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, Howard (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, Hylan G. (Box A-74, Folder 3)
    - Lewis, Ida (Box A-74, Folder 4)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Monroe S. Frederick II, Dan Entin,
    - Lewis, Ira Foster (Box A-74, Folder 5)
    - Lewis, Ida Mary (Box A-74, Folder 6)
    - Lewis, Isaiah (Box A-74, Folder 7)
    - Lewis, Ivy (Box A-74, Folder 8)
    - Lewis, Jackie (Box A-74, Folder 9)
    - Lewis, Johnny (Box A-74, Folder 10)
    - Lewis, John H. (Box A-74, Folder 11)
      Also two newspaper clippings and one typescript press release (two leaves) with ms. leaf attached with paperclip. One print has single-leaf press release attached with paperclip.
    - Lewis, John G., Jr. (Box A-74, Folder 12)
    - Lewis, John (Box A-74, Folder 13)
      Photographer if identified: W.B. Burke
    - Lewis, John (Box A-74, Folder 14)
    - Lewis, John (Box A-74, Folder 15)
    - Lewis, John (Box A-74, Folder 16)
    - Lewis, J. (Box A-74, Folder 17)
    - Lewis, John (Box A-74, Folder 18)
    - Lewis, John (Box A-74, Folder 19)
      One print has typescript press release (two leaves) attached with a paperclip; also a single-leaf press release.
    - Lewis, James (Box A-74, Folder 20)
    - Lewis, James (Box A-74, Folder 21)
      Print is cut out.
    - Lewis, James (Box A-74, Folder 22)
      Note on folder: "See Nathaniel Dickerson"
    - Lewis, Jennifer (Box A-74, Folder 23)
    - Lewis, Jimmy (Box A-74, Folder 24)
    - Lewis, Jimmy, Jr. (Box A-74, Folder 25)
    - Lewis, Jimmy "Baby Face" (Box A-74, Folder 26)
    - Lewis, Joey III (Box A-74, Folder 27)
    - Lewis, Joseph (Box A-74, Folder 28)
    - Lewis, Juanita (Box A-74, Folder 29)
    - Lewis, Katherine Handy (Box A-74, Folder 30)
    - Lewis, Landon (Box A-74, Folder 31)
    - Lewis, Laura (Box A-74, Folder 32)
    - Lewis, Lawrence (Box A-74, Folder 33)
    - Lewis, Lawrence, L. (Box A-74, Folder 34)
      Photographer if identified: Joe Covello/Black Star
    - Lewis, Lenny (& Orchestra) (Box A-74, Folder 35)
    - Lewis, Leon (Box A-74, Folder 36)
      Photographer if identified: Negro Press Photo Service, Bro. David McAdams
    - Lewis, Linda (Box A-74, Folder 37)
      Photographer if identified: The Bayside Studio
    - Lewis, Linda (Box A-74, Folder 38)
    - Lewis, Lindsay (Box A-74, Folder 39)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Gill Photographers
    - Lewis, Loida Nicolas (Box A-74, Folder 40)
    - Lewis, Mabel (Box A-74, Folder 41)
    - Lewis, Martha (Box A-74, Folder 42)
      One print has single typescript leaf adhered on verso.
    - Lewis, Maybelle (Box A-74, Folder 43)
    - Lewis, Magdalene Dorothy (Box A-74, Folder 44)
    - Lewis, Mahlon (Rev.) (Box A-74, Folder 45)
    - Lewis, Mallory Jane (Box A-74, Folder 46)
      Photographer if identified: Nat Purefoy
    - Lewis, Margaret (Box A-74, Folder 47)
    - Lewis, Margaret (Box A-74, Folder 48)
    - Lewis, Margaret (Box A-74, Folder 49)
    - Lewis, Margaret R. (Box A-74, Folder 50)
      Photographer if identified: Milton McPhail
    - Lewis, Marie (Box A-74, Folder 51)
    - Lewis, Martin (Box A-74, Folder 52)
      Photographer if identified: Mort Tucker
    - Lewis, Martha (Box A-74, Folder 53)
      Photographer if identified: N.Y.C. Housing Authority Photo Unit, Burley Photo Syndicate
    - Lewis, Marva (Box A-74, Folder 54)
    - Lewis, Mary (Box A-74, Folder 55)
    - Lewis, Mel (Box A-74, Folder 56)
    - Lewis, Mildred (Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 57)
    - Lewis, Nathaniel (Box A-74, Folder 58)
      Photographer if identified: Hayes Photographers
    - Lewis, Norman (Box A-74, Folder 59)
      Four prints have single-leaf press releases attached.
      Photographer if identified: Alan Mercer
    - Lewis, Patrick (Box A-74, Folder 60)
    - Lewis, Patrick (Box A-74, Folder 61)
    - Lewis, Pauthea (Box A-74, Folder 62)
    - Lewis, Philson (Box A-74, Folder 63)
    - Lewis, Ray (Box A-74, Folder 64)
    - Lewis, Ramsey (Box A-74, Folder 65)
    - Lewis, Reginald F. (Box A-74, Folder 66)
    - Lewis, Reinaldo Sgt. (Box A-74, Folder 67)
    - Lewis, Robert (Box A-74, Folder 68)
    - Lewis, Ron (Box A-74, Folder 69)
    - Lewis, Ronald (Dr.) (Box A-74, Folder 70)
    - Lewis, Ronnie (Box A-74, Folder 71)
    - Lewis, Rufus A. (Box A-74, Folder 72)
    - Lewis, Sarah (Box A-74, Folder 73)
    - Lewis, Shawn (Box A-74, Folder 74)
      Also two velox prints stuck together.
    - Lewis, Shelton (Box A-74, Folder 75)
      Photographer if identified: Nel-Mae Studio
    - Lewis, Stewart (Box A-74, Folder 76)
    - Lewis, Stewart (Box A-74, Folder 77)
      Print has staple on border.
      Photographer if identified: Ace Creative Photos
    - Lewis, Sybil (Box A-74, Folder 78)
    - Lewis, Thelma (Box A-74, Folder 79)
    - Lewis, Thelma W. (Box A-74, Folder 80)
      Print has press release (one typescript leaf letter, one typescript leaf press release and one photocopied leaf) attached with staple on border.
    - Lewis, Tony (Box A-74, Folder 81)
    - Lewis, Virginia (Box A-74, Folder 82)
    - Lewis, W. Arthur (Dr.) (Box A-74, Folder 83)
    - Lewis, Walter (Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 84)
    - Lewis, Walter B. (Box A-74, Folder 85)
    - Lewis, Webster (Box A-74, Folder 86)
    - Lewis, Wilhelmina (Box A-74, Folder 87)
    - Lewis, William (Box A-74, Folder 88)
    - Lewis, William (Box A-74, Folder 89)
    - Lewis, Wm. (Box A-74, Folder 90)
      One print has typescript press release (two leaves) attached with staple on border.
      Photographer if identified: Wagner International Photo
    - Lewis, Wm. (Box A-74, Folder 91)
    - Lewis, William B. (Box A-74, Folder 92)
    - Lewis, Willie & Harry (Box A-74, Folder 93)
      Photographer if identified: L. Hutchinson, Rapid News Photo
    - Lewis, Willie (Baton) (Box A-74, Folder 94)
    - Lewis, Woodrow (Box A-74, Folder 95)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Dave Greene Photo,
    - Lewis, Zelma (Box A-74, Folder 96)
    - Lewisohn Stadium (Box A-74, Folder 97)
      Photographer if identified: Alix B. Williamson
    - Lewitt, Arthur (Box A-74, Folder 98)
    - Lewter, Andrew C. (Box A-74, Folder 99)
    - Lexington School of Deaf (Box A-74, Folder 100)
    - Leyba, Claire (Box A-74, Folder 101)
      Photographer if identified: Chidnoff, Mme. Yvonne A.R.P.S., Chet Ross
    - LeZama, Carlos (Box A-74, Folder 102)
    - Liberation Dance Co. (Box A-74, Folder 103)
    - Liberation Day (Box A-74, Folder 104)
    - Liberia (Box A-74, Folder 105)
    - Liberty Weekend (Box A-74, Folder 106)
      Note on folder: "1986" and "Military Precision."
    - Libra Cosmetics (Box A-74, Folder 107)
    - Libra (Box A-74, Folder 108)
      Print has ms. writing on verso.
    - Licorish, David (Rev.) (Box A-74, Folder 109)
      One print is mounted on cardboard. Also two velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Bro. David McAdams, Cecil Layne, James Gilbert, Granville Allen, A. Hansen, Harris Photo, Negro Press Photo Service Inc.
    - Liddie, William S. (Box A-74, Folder 110)
      One print has single typescript leaf pres release attached with paperclip. Also one velox print.
    - Lieben, Margie (Mrs. + Family) (Box A-74, Folder 111)
    - Life, Reggie (Box A-74, Folder 112)
    - Lifeene, Robert (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 113)
    - Liford, Sallie (Box A-74, Folder 114)
      Photographer if identified: Erman's Studio
    - Liggins, Betty (Box A-74, Folder 115)
    - Lightfoot, Harrison (Box A-74, Folder 116)
      Photographer if identified: George Hopkins
    - Lightfood, Michaux (Box A-74, Folder 117)
      Photographer if identified: Clifton Cabell
    - Lightfoot, Robert (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 118)
    - Lightner, Marguerit (Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 119)
    - Like It Is (Box A-74, Folder 120)
    - Lile, Ford (Box A-74, Folder 121)
    - Lilly, Edward (Box A-74, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: Philip J. Carvalho
    - Lilienthal, Brenda (Box A-74, Folder 123)
      Photographer if identified: Negro Press Photo Service
    - Lilienthal, Jean (Box A-74, Folder 124)
    - Lilley, A. Lors (Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 125)
    - Lilly, Charles (Box A-74, Folder 126)
    - Lilly, Mary (Box A-74, Folder 127)
    - Lima, Rose (Box A-74, Folder 128)
    - Limelites (Group) (Box A-74, Folder 129)
    - Limerick, Daniel (Box A-74, Folder 130)
    - Lin, W.J.G. (Rev.) (Box A-74, Folder 131)
    - Linares, Rosalind (Box A-74, Folder 132)
    - Lincoln Center (Box A-74, Folder 133)
      Prints have four typescript press releases (four leaves, five leaves, six leaves, three leaves and one leaf on colored paper) attached with paperclip.
    - Lincoln, Abbey (Box A-74, Folder 134)
      One print has newspaper clipping adhered on verso. One typescript press release (two leaves).
      Photographer if identified: Ronnie Brathwaite, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Price, Harris Photo, Al Burley, Ace Creative Photo, Risasi-Zachariah Dais, Negro Press Photo Service Inc
    - Lincoln, Abe (Box A-74, Folder 135)
      Photographer if identified: Clay Descant, International News Photo, Roger Smith, Lincoln-Mercury, The Big Four News Photo Service, American Museum Of Natural History
    - Lincoln, Eric C. (Box A-74, Folder 136)
    - Lincoln, Henry (Box A-74, Folder 137)
    - Lincoln, Richard (Box A-74, Folder 138)
      Also one ink drawing.
    - Lincoln Hospital (Box A-74, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: Louis Checkman
    - Lincoln High School (Box A-74, Folder 140)
    - Lincoln University (Box A-74, Folder 141)
      Both prints have single-leaf press releases attached.
    - Lind, Dionecio (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 142)
    - Lindsay, Eddie (Box A-74, Folder 143)
      Photographer if identified: Zito Studio
    - Lindsay, Egbert (Box A-74, Folder 144)
    - Lindsay, Erwinna (Box A-74, Folder 145)
    - Lindsay, Erwinna (Box A-74, Folder 146)
    - Lindsay, Gilbert W. (Box A-74, Folder 147)
      Photographer if identified: Guy Crowder
    - Lindsay, Gladys (Box A-74, Folder 148)
    - Lindsay, Isabel B. (Dr.) (Box A-74, Folder 149)
    - Lindsay, Isabel (Box A-74, Folder 150)
    - Lindsay, Baron (Box A-74, Folder 151)
    - Lindqvist, Joyce (Box A-74, Folder 152)
    - Lindsay, Claudia (Box A-74, Folder 153)
      One print has promotional pamphlet attached.
    - Lindsay, Kevin (Box A-74, Folder 154)
    - Lindsay, John (Box A-74, Folder 155)
    - Lindsay, Powell (Box A-74, Folder 156)
      Four prints are stuck together; one is stuck to folder; one has newspaper clipping on verso; one has single typescript letter attached; two have typescript captions attached; also single typescript press release.
      Photographer if identified: Roslyn Bramms, Cecil Layne, Gilbert Pictorial Service, James Gilbert
    - Lindsay, Sidney (Box A-74, Folder 157)
      Photographer if identified: Portfolio International Inc. House Of Creative Photography
    - Lindsay, William L. (Box A-74, Folder 158)
    - Lunette's Lounge (Box A-74, Folder 159)
    - Linnwood, Mr. & Mrs. W. H. (Box A-74, Folder 160)
    - Lindsey, Arnett G. (Box A-74, Folder 161)
    - Lindsey, Claudia (Box A-74, Folder 162)
    - Lindsey, James H. (Box A-74, Folder 163)
    - Lindsey, Sadie (Box A-74, Folder 164)
    - Lindsey, Rev. Wm. (Box A-74, Folder 165)
    - Link, John (Box A-74, Folder 166)
    - Link, Ronald (Box A-74, Folder 167)
    - Linkletter, Art (Box A-74, Folder 168)
    - Links (Bklyn Chapter) (Box A-74, Folder 169)
    - Links (Bklyn) (Box A-74, Folder 170)
      Note on folder: "Salute to Youth."
    - Links, Buffalo Chapter (Box A-74, Folder 171)
    - Lint, Alfred (Box A-74, Folder 172)
    - Linticum, Alice (Box A-74, Folder 173)
      Photographer if identified: Bernard Of Hollywood
    - Linton, Adulphius (Box A-74, Folder 174)
      Print is adhered to paper.
    - Linton, Linda (Box A-74, Folder 175)
      Note on folder: "Principal P.S. 23."
      Photographer if identified: Cameron Studios, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Linton, Janet (Box A-74, Folder 176)
      Photographer if identified: Beach & Barnes
    - Linton, Ray (Box A-74, Folder 177)
    - Linton, Terry (Box A-74, Folder 178)
    - Linyard, Richard (Box A-74, Folder 179)
    - Lion's Club (Box A-74, Folder 180)
    - Lioness Club (Box A-74, Folder 181)
    - Lipman, Wynona (Dr.) (Box A-74, Folder 182)
      Photographer if identified: Ed Kamper
    - Lipscomb, Clifford N. (Box A-74, Folder 183)
    - Lipscomb, Gene (Box A-74, Folder 184)
    - Lipper, Ken (Box A-74, Folder 185)
      Photographer if identified: Larry Bown, Anne Day
    - Lippman, Marc (Box A-74, Folder 186)
    - Lipscomb, Henry P., Jr. (Box A-74, Folder 187)
    - Lipscomb, Ronald (Box A-74, Folder 188)
    - Lipscombe, Laura (Box A-74, Folder 189)
      Pint has single typescript leaf caption on verso.
    - Lipset, William (Box A-74, Folder 190)
    - Lipsett, Percival (Dr.) (Box A-74, Folder 191)
    - Lipsig, Harry (Box A-74, Folder 192)
    - Liquor Industry (Box A-74, Folder 193)
    - Liscomb, Jesse (Box A-74, Folder 194)
      One print is attached to a piece of cardstock.
    - Liscomb, Jesse R., Jr. (Dr.) (Box A-74, Folder 195)
    - Lisser, Stanley R. (Box A-74, Folder 196)
    - Lissoko, Dabo (Hon.) (Box A-74, Folder 197)
    - Liston, H (Box A-74, Folder 198)
    - Liston, Louise (Box A-74, Folder 199)
    - Liston, Melba (Box A-74, Folder 200)
      Photographer if identified: Raymond Ross, Ted Davis
    - Liston, Robin (Box A-74, Folder 201)
    - Liston, Sonny (Box A-74, Folder 202)
    - Litchfield, Robert (Box A-74, Folder 203)
    - Lites, Michael (Box A-74, Folder 204)
      Photographer if identified: Freelance-East/Robert Johnson
    - Lites, Ronald (Box A-74, Folder 205)
    - Litt, Max (Box A-74, Folder 206)
    - Little, Alpha D. (Box A-74, Folder 207)
    - Little, Arthur (Box A-74, Folder 208)
      Photographer if identified: Ernest C. Withers
    - Little Anthony (Box A-74, Folder 209)
      Print has single photocopied leaf press release attached.
    - Little, B.A. (Box A-74, Folder 210)
    - Little, Col. Arthur W. (Box A-74, Folder 211)
    - Little, C. (Box A-74, Folder 212)
    - Little, Cleavon (Box A-74, Folder 213)
      Four prints have single-leaf press releases attached. Also five velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Zodiac Photographers, Harris Photo, Raymond Ross
    - Little, C. L. (Dr.) (Box A-74, Folder 214)
    - Little, Delores (Box A-74, Folder 215)
    - Little, Diana G. (Box A-74, Folder 216)
    - "Little Dion" (Box A-74, Folder 217)
    - Little, Eugene (Box A-74, Folder 218)
      Photographer if identified: Andrea W. Kaufman
    - Little, Floyd (Box A-74, Folder 219)
    - Little, Floyd (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 220)
    - Little, Henrietta (Box A-74, Folder 221)
    - Littell, Blaine (Box A-74, Folder 222)
    - Little, George (Rev.) (Box A-74, Folder 223)
      Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams, Alex Hamilton
    - Little, Hannah B. (Box A-74, Folder 224)
    - Little, Harlee H. (Box A-74, Folder 225)
    - Little, Henrietta (Box A-74, Folder 226)
    - Little, Iris A. (Box A-74, Folder 227)
    - Little, Joan (Box A-74, Folder 228)
      Three prints have lengthy typescript captions attached on recto. Also four velox prints.
    - Little, Vera (Box A-74, Folder 229)
    - Littlejohn, Cheryl (Box A-74, Folder 230)
    - Littlejohn, Elinor (Box A-74, Folder 231)
    - Littlejohn, Harriet (Box A-74, Folder 232)
    - Littlejohn, James (Box A-74, Folder 233)
    - Littlejohn, Joseph (Phil) (Box A-74, Folder 234)
      Print has typescript press release (two leaves) from Jersey State College attached with paperclip.
    - Littlejohn, Roy (Box A-74, Folder 235)
    - Littlejohn, Stanley (Box A-74, Folder 236)
    - Little Leaguers (Box A-74, Folder 237)
    - Littleton, Edsel M. (Box A-74, Folder 238)
      Print has single typescript press release from Proctor & Gamble attached with paperclip.
    - Littleton, Emma (Box A-74, Folder 239)
    - Little Miss Black America (Box A-74, Folder 240)
      One print is mounted on paper and features Randy Jackson of the Jackson 5.
    - "Little Richard" (Box A-74, Folder 241)
    - Little Rock, Ark., Riot (Box A-74, Folder 242)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Gene Prescott, Bro. David McAdams
    - LIttles, Avon (Box A-74, Folder 243)
    - Littles, Dolores A. (Box A-74, Folder 244)
    - Littles, Ernest (Box A-74, Folder 245)
    - Littles, Sarah (Box A-74, Folder 246)
    - "Livin' Fat" (Box A-74, Folder 247)
      One print has computer typescript printed playbill and typescript press release (two leaves) from the Billie Holiday Theatre attached. Also one velox print.
    - Livingstone College (Box A-74, Folder 248)
      Also one velox print. One print has single-leaf press release attached with paperclip. Four prints have 13 typescript press release leaves attached with paperclips (leaves appear to have been singed in a fire).
    - Livingston, Elaine (Box A-74, Folder 249)
      Note on folder: "On picture with Lola Rivera."
    - Livingston, Louise (Box A-74, Folder 250)
      Also one negative (two images).
    - Livingston, Patrice (Box A-74, Folder 251)
      Photographer if identified: Marianne Barcellona
    - Livisay, Frances (Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 252)
    - Livisay, Leonidas (Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 253)
      Note on folder: "See Dr. S. A. Gadsby"
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne/Layne's Studio, Margot Kaiser
    - Lizzie (Chiz) (Box A-74, Folder 254)
    - Llewelyn, J. Bruce (Box A-74, Folder 255)
      Two prints have newspaper clippings on verso. Also one velox print and three velox prints stuck together.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Dalman James Jr., Q. T. Vincent, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
      Number of Prints: 38
    - Llewelyn, Sid (Box A-74, Folder 256)
    - Lloyd, Bobby E. (Box A-74, Folder 257)
    - Lloyd, Charles (Box A-74, Folder 258)
      Photographer if identified: Drake Studios
    - Lloyd, Clement (Mrs.) (Box A-74, Folder 259)
      Photographer if identified: Pope's Studio
    - Lloyd, Corenna (Box A-74, Folder 260)
    - Lloyd, Dee (Box A-74, Folder 261)
    - Lloyd, Dorothy (Miss) (Box A-74, Folder 262)
    - Lloyd, Darryle (Box A-74, Folder 263)
      Note on verso: "Hemodialysis for Blacks."
      Photographer if identified: James Pozarik
    - Lloyd, Dorothy (Box A-74, Folder 264)
      Photographer if identified: Dorothy Lloyd
    - Lloyd, Earl (Box A-74, Folder 265)
    - Lloyd, Edna (Box A-74, Folder 266)
    - Lloyd, Edward (Box A-74, Folder 267)
    - Lloyd, George (Rev.) (Box A-74, Folder 268)
    - Lloyd, Ivan (Dr.) (Box A-74, Folder 269)
    - Lloyd, Lillian S. (Rev.) (Box A-74, Folder 270)
    - Lloyd, Nathaniel T. (Rev.) (Box A-74, Folder 271)
    - Lloyd, Ruby (Box A-74, Folder 272)
    - Lloyd, Samuel Rev. (Box A-74, Folder 273)
    - Lloyd, Shawn & Cecil (Box A-74, Folder 274)
    - Lloyd, Tom (Box A-74, Folder 275)
    - Lloyd, William H. (Box A-74, Folder 276)
    - Lobadie, Lunel (Box A-74, Folder 277)
    - Lobban, Ether (Box A-74, Folder 278)
    - Local 802/144/1549 (Box A-74, Folder 279)
      Photographer if identified: Rapid News Studios, Standard Studios
    - Local 1199 (Box A-74, Folder 280)
      One print has staple on border.
    - Local 1199 (Box A-74, Folder 281)
      Also one velox print. Three prints have paste residue on verso.
      Number of Prints: 17
    - Local Citizenship Participation Inc. (Box A-74, Folder 282)
    - Locality Mayor's Comm. of New York (Box A-74, Folder 283)
      Photographer if identified: Photography by Wilson
    - Locke, Alain (Box A-74, Folder 284)
      Prints are images of paintings. Also one velox print.
    - Locker, Jesse D. (Box A-74, Folder 285)
      Photographer if identified: Maiy's, Dummett
    - Lockerman, Gloria (Box A-74, Folder 286)
      Three prints have been cut out.
    - Locket, Sandra (Box A-74, Folder 287)
    - Lockett, Bert (Box A-74, Folder 288)
    - Lockett, Edgar (Box A-74, Folder 289)
      Photographer if identified: L. H. Davis
    - Lockett, Eleanor (Box A-74, Folder 290)
    - Lockett, Francis (Box A-74, Folder 291)
    - Lloyd, Lucille (Box A-74, Folder 292)
    - Lockett, Joan (Mrs.) (Box A-75, Folder 1)
      Photographer if identified: Cress Studios
    - Lockett, St. Charles (Box A-75, Folder 2)
    - Lockett, Stephen N. (Box A-75, Folder 3)
      Also two velox prints and one press release.
      Photographer if identified: Tommy Weber
    - Lockett, Viola (Box A-75, Folder 4)
    - Lockey, Kenneth (Box A-75, Folder 5)
    - Lockhart, Al (Box A-75, Folder 6)
    - Lockhart, Barbara (Box A-75, Folder 7)
    - Lockhart, Calvin (Box A-75, Folder 8)
      Photographer if identified: Lensman
    - Lockhart, Carl (Box A-75, Folder 9)
    - Lockhart, James W. (Box A-75, Folder 10)
    - Lockhart, Jewell (Box A-75, Folder 11)
    - Lockhart, Juanita (Box A-75, Folder 12)
    - Lockhart, Keith E. (Box A-75, Folder 13)
    - Lockhart, Marjorie (Box A-75, Folder 14)
      Photographer if identified: Ralph D. Arnett
    - Lockhart, Nora Evans (Box A-75, Folder 15)
    - Lockhart (Rev.) (Box A-75, Folder 16)
    - Lockhart, Sharon (Box A-75, Folder 17)
      Print has résumé stapled to verso.
    - Lockhart, Spider (Box A-75, Folder 18)
    - Lockett, Stephen (Box A-75, Folder 19)
    - Locklair, L. A. (Box A-75, Folder 20)
    - Lockley, Christal (Box A-75, Folder 21)
    - Lockman, Irvin C. (Rev.) (Box A-75, Folder 22)
    - Lockman, Nolan (Box A-75, Folder 23)
    - Lockman, Ronald (Pvt.) (Box A-75, Folder 24)
    - Lockmann, Ike (Box A-75, Folder 25)
    - Lockwood, George (Rev.) (Box A-75, Folder 26)
      Photographer if identified: Harold T. Cooper, Gill Photographers
    - Loco, Joe (Box A-75, Folder 27)
      Photographer if identified: Moss Photo
    - Locus, Cassandra (Box A-75, Folder 28)
    - Lodge, Boyer (Box A-75, Folder 29)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot (Box A-75, Folder 30)
    - Lodge, John (Box A-75, Folder 31)
      Photographer if identified: John Vignoli
    - Loding, Joyce B. (Mrs.) (Box A-75, Folder 32)
    - Loeb, Ralph (Rev. & Mrs.) (Box A-75, Folder 33)
      Photographer if identified: W. Smith, Rapid News Service
    - Loengard, R. O. (Mrs.) (Box A-75, Folder 34)
    - Loftin, Beatrice (Box A-75, Folder 35)
    - Loftin, Clarence C. III (Box A-75, Folder 36)